Hello my dear friends prati din mato nen chakari pratibandhan tu madar ke jana punra swagato
aaj ke tu madar ke update debo
ICICI Lord General Insurance Company
Limited sanstha chakari vacancy
sapke to bandura chakari vista tath java
aage tumhar ka request a channel ke must
subscribe kar niyo
ICICI Loeb General Insurance Company besh
kti nil post tar company Unit Sales
Manager paday pratyak neb
ICICI Loeb Sanstha ta Unit Sales
Manager paday pratyak nikal karb working
interview upar
bhirat interview ansh grahan kari pratyak
dress code
formal hote
Unit Sales Manager paday jan
ICICI Lord Sanstha tan dhj bare 2 la hj ta thake up
to 4 lakh tak ma eva sange de company
rules anujay a nannya anek neek sukita
Unit Sales Manager paday full time and
permanent jab eva
chakari ho direct ICICI Loeb General
Insurance Company Limited
sanspele interview de samay jj document gu
lagab seg holo updated resume  Aadhar and
PAN card, Xerox of all educational qualification
certificates. Candidates
can apply for Unit Manager post but they should be at least
above the age of 18 years. For
ICICI Lodha Institute of Unit Sales Manager,
candidates must have passed
minimum graduation from any Government recognized educational institution and must have
basic knowledge of computer along with fluency in
regional language.
Unit Sales Manager post work is to
source health insurance through agents, hire agents
and provide training to agents through the
prescribed dewa kaka, get the bank account
through agents, get regular license and
tracking sanction, get the bank registered
with the Law Department,
get regular appointments with agents and lead providers and get the data protected through
ICICI Lodha Institute.
Applicants are applying but
no applicant is
eligible for the
post. Please
give me information about the video description box. ICICI Lombard is hiring for the post of Unit
Sales Manager. The
interview process will be started on 19th
February. The interview will be held
till Wednesday, 28th February, from 9:30 AM to
5:30
PM. The interview will be conducted at the office of
ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company
Limited, Seventh Floor, Apjoy House, 15, Mother
Teresa Saroni, Taltala,
Kolkata, Pin No.
716. Contact Person: Mr. Sandeep
Das, Unit Sales Manager, Post Paschim Bange, All India Anna Dravida Munnetra Kazhagam.
Applicants are applying but the
nominated applicant is posted at the office of
ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Limited, from 15, Mother Teresa Saroni, Taltala, Kolkata, Pin No. 716. Applicants are applying but the nominated applicant is posted at the office of ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company
Limited, from 15, Mother Teresa Saroni, Taltala, Kolkata, Pin No. 716.
Check Chalk Information Below